Tufts Dental Medicine (Dental Alumni Magazine) UP154
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Dental Medicine (Dental Alumni Magazine)
1996 -- 2015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Alumni Association
UP154
1.2 Linear Feet
12 Digital Object(s)
154.1 Megabytes
1 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Tufts Dental Magazine containing information and news about Tufts School of Dental Medicine and dental alumni. Briefly known as "Dental Alumni Record." Originally published as "Tufts Alumni Record"
- Tufts Dental Medicine (Dental Alumni Magazine), 1996 -- 2018; UP154.001; 1.2 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s); 154.1 Megabytes; 1 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Tufts Dental Magazine. It has information and news about Tufts School of Dental Medicine and dental alumni. Briefly known as "Dental Alumni Record." Originally published as "Tufts Alumni Record"
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Dental Alumni Record, Fall, 1996; UP154.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Dental Alumni Record, Spring, 1997; UP154.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    1, 2
  - Dental Alumni Record, Winter, 1997 -- 1998; UP154.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    2, 1
  - Dental Alumni Record, Summer, 1998; UP154.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    2, 2
  - Dental Alumni Record, Winter, 1998; UP154.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    2nd copy (bound volume) in Reading Room
    3, 1
  - Dental Alumni Record, Summer, 1999; UP154.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    3, 2
  - Dental Alumni Record, Winter, 1999; UP154.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    4, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2000; UP154.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    4, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2000; UP154.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    5, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2001; UP154.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    5, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2001; UP154.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    6, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2002; UP154.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    6, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2002; UP154.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    7, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2003; UP154.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    7, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2003; UP154.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    8, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2004; UP154.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    8, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2005; UP154.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    9, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2005; UP154.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    9, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2006; UP154.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    10, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2006; UP154.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    10, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2007; UP154.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    11, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2007; UP154.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2008; UP154.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    12, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2008; UP154.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    12, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2009; UP154.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    13, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2009; UP154.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    13, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2010; UP154.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
    14, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2010; UP154.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
    14, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2011; UP154.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
    15, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2011; UP154.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
    15, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2012; UP154.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
    16, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2012; UP154.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    16, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2013; UP154.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    17, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2013; UP154.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
    17, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2014; UP154.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
    18, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2014; UP154.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
    18, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2015; UP154.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
    19, 1
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2015; UP154.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
    19, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Summer, 2016; UP154.001.001.00039 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Volume, number
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2018; UP154.001.001.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Volume, Number
    22, 2
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Winter, 2016; UP154.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2017; UP154.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Fall, 2017; UP154.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring 2017 -- Spring 2019; UP154.000047; 1 Volumes (Volume 1)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Barbara Lewis, Administrative Coordinator for Communications and Marketing, 2022, accession UA-2023-026.
  - Tufts Dental Medicine, Spring, 2018; UP154.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s)